chiccoshop.com 2019-04-11

# eCommerce Solutions On-Demand | Demandware Privacy Policy

## Chicco Privacy Policy

Your privacy is extremely important to us, and, as such, we will strive to keep your personal information confidential and avoid unwanted solicitations. This Privacy Policy explains the type of personal information we collect and how we intend to use it. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we collect and safeguard your personal information.

**Collection of Personal Information**

You can browse the majority of this site without providing any personal information. However, surveys, giveaways, contests, etc., which are strictly voluntary, may require your personal information for the purpose of marketing communication.

**What Are Cookies?**

"Cookies" are small data files that your web browser reads and stores on your hard drive when you connect to our website. Their primary function is to help us remember you for our statistics — and specifically, the computer and web browser you're using — by collecting non-personally identifiable information (such as your IP address and browser type). This allows us to provide you with a better, more relevant shopping experience by improving our site's navigation and content. Cookies also help us determine which features and tools you use, and which pages you visit on ChiccoUSA.com.

**How We Use Cookies**

We do not use cookies to glean any personal information about you or track your movements on the Internet outside of those pages you visit on ChiccoUSA.com. If you have any concerns about leaving cookies on your computer for extended periods, you can delete them using your browser preferences or privacy menus.

**Opting Out / Email Address Removal**

We want to communicate to you only if you would like to hear from us! If you prefer not to receive emails from ChiccoUSA.com, please let us know. There are 2 easy options for opting out. 1) Contact [Customer Service](http://www.chiccousa.com/contactus) or calling 1-877-424-4226. 2) You may also click the unsubscribe link located under any email you receive from ChiccoUSA.com. The unsubscribe link is located at the very bottom of all email communications.

**Use of Personal Information**

The information collected through product registration is used to ensure our continued superior customer service and to notify you immediately regarding any issues affecting your product. At no time will we use your product registration information for marketing purposes. The information collected through surveys, giveaways, contests, etc. may be used to ensure our continued superior customer service, improve our product offerings, and keep you apprised of our latest product announcements, special offers and other matters of general interest. While this information may be used for marketing and promotional purposes within our company, we will not intentionally share your information with anyone outside of our company, unless required to do so by law. We will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information. We will not, however, be liable for the disclosure of information which results from errors in transmission or unauthorized acts by third parties.

**Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not knowingly solicit, collect or use personal information from users under the age of 13. In fact, users under the age of 13 must not submit information to the interactive areas of the Chicco website. We may ask users to state their age when appropriate to verify compliance with these policies.

**Linked Sites**

This website contains links to third-party websites. While we do not intentionally share your personal information with these third-parties, you should be aware that we maintain no control over these entities and are not responsible for their privacy practices. Accordingly, we encourage you to learn more about the privacy policies of these companies.

**Security**

We have implemented a number of security features to attempt to prevent the unauthorized release of, or access to, information provided by this Site. Please be advised, however, that although we have endeavored to create a secure and reliable website, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted via the Chicco Site or via e-mail cannot be guaranteed. You should always remain mindful of the fact that any information disclosed via the Internet is potentially accessible by unauthorized persons and, consequently, may be collected by such unauthorized persons and used without our consent. We disclaim all liability for the security of information transmitted through the Internet.

**Special Cases**

We reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our websites, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation.

**Changes**

We are the sole owner of the aggregated information collected on the Chicco Site. In the event we go through a business transition or change of control, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, the information we have received from you on this website may be among the assets transferred.

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage all users to review this policy regularly for any such changes.

Most recent revision date: 04/08/2018
